(DINOSAUR GRUMBLES)
(FISHING LINE WHIZZES)
(MAN HUMMING)
Any minute now. You see,
you can't rush it, baby girl.
The secret to fishing
is patience.
It's been
five hours, Dad.
How much more patience
do we need?
Don't ask me.
Ask the fish.
(GROANS)
(YAWNS)
What's up, guys?
It's your boy, Dustin.
I'm out on the boat,
and once again,
my dad can't catch
any fish.
Hey! I heard that.
Don't worry, sweetheart,
I caught these this morning.
At the grocery store.
Mom, I'm live!
So embarrassing!
(MEOWS)
(YOWLS)
MOM: Mr. Fluffy Butt, no!
Bad kitty!
Whoa.
Uh... Dad?
(GASPS)
Dad!
Shh! Quiet.
You'll scare the fishies.
The boat's on fire!
(YELPS)
(GIRL AND MOM SCREAMS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Down! Ready... set.
Ruff!
(PUPS PANTING)
Skye! Skye, I'm open!
Marshall, go long!
I got it. I got it. I-- Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
Oof!
(PUPS GIGGLE)
ALL: Marshall!
I'm okay!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Pass is incomplete.
Flag on the play.
Ten yards for clumsiness.
(PUPS LAUGH)
(BEEPS, CRACKLES)
DAD: (OVER RADIO)
Mayday, mayday! S.O.S.!
Our cat set our boat on fire!
This is the PAW Patrol.
S.O.S. received.
We're on our way.
(SIREN BLARES)
Come on, pups.
Ryder needs us.
That was my first touchdown!
It's still gonna count, right?
Hey, wait up!
RYDER: All right, pups.
(BEEPS)
We've got
a five-alarm boat fire
and there are people onboard.
Zuma, you are go for launch.
Aye-aye, Ryder, sir!
(BEEPS)
(WHOOSHES)
(HOWLS)
(FANS WHIR)
RYDER: Skye, let's get eyes
on that boat ASAP.
I'm on it.
Marshall, Chase, Rubble,
let's fight that fire.
Hoses on!
Help! Up here!
Help!
We're up here!
My name's Zuma
and I'll be your rescue pup.
(SLIDE SQUEAKS)
All right!
Oh, thank goodness.
It's time for you dudes
to ride the slide.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
Oh! (GIGGLES)
(MOM LAUGHS)
Whoo!
RYDER: All right, pups,
it's showtime!
(PUPS HOWL)
Man, this video is fire!
Dustin, get off your phone
and evacuate.
Oh. Gotta go.
Like and subscribe.
Hup! Whoo-hoo!
(CLICKS TONGUE)
That's everyone.
(BEEPS)
Whoo-hoo!
RYDER: Nice work, Zuma.
(GASPS)
The cat!
Hey, where's Mr. Fluffy Butt?
He must still be onboard.
(PARENTS GASP)
Mr. Fluffy Butt!
Pups, we've got a cat onboard.
It's always a cat.
Stuck in a tree,
stuck in a boat...
Don't worry. I'm on it.
(GRUNTS)
(WHOOSHES)
(HELMET BEEPS, WHIRS)
Okay, Marshall.
No clumsiness, no mistakes.
(STAIR CREAKS)
(SING-SONGY) Here, kitty,
kitty, kitty! Hello!
Mr. Fluffy Butt!
Kitty, where are you?
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Looks like we're gonna have
to do this the hard way.
Fire axes!
(GRUNTING)
(MEOWS)
I found the kitty.
He's actually pretty cute.
For a cat.
(GASPS)
RYDER: (OVER RADIO) Marshall,
your exit is blocked.
You're gonna have to find
another way out.
Copy that.
Sorry about this, kitty.
(YOWLS)
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED YOWL)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL EXHALE)
MOM: Oh, no!
DAD: Come on, man.
Where are they?
No...
Oh, no.
(MARSHALL GASPS)
(ALL CHEER)
Yeah!
That wasn't so bad,
was it, kitty?
(YOWLS WEAKLY)
Come to mommy.
Oh, my baby. Mwah.
Ugh. Are you sure
that's Mr. Fluffy Butt?
(MR. FLUFFY BUTT GROWLS)
Don't worry.
His butt will fluff up again
as soon as he dries off.
Loop, swoop, and pull.
(CHUCKLES)
All right,
the hitch is hooked!
Don't worry, kids.
Captain Turbot is the O.G.
of the high seas.
He'll have us back
to land in no time.
You know it!
(FOGHORN BLARES)
Goodbye, Cap'n Turbot!
Goodbye!
Farewell, friends!
Bye!
See you later!
Stay cool,
little doggies!
Bye, Mr. Fluffy Butt!
Nice work, Marshall.
That was a perfect rescue.
What can I say?
Rescue pups
don't make mistakes.
(ALERT BEEPING)
Looks like we're heading
into some weather.
Buckle up, pups.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
PUPS: Whoa!
Whoa!
Isn't this fun?
(GAGS)
(GROANS) I think
I'm more of a land mammal.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Switch on the fog lights!
Switching on fog lights.
(THUNDER CRASHES, RUMBLES)
(ALARM BEEPING)
Ryder,
we're drifting off course.
(RYDER GROANS)
I'm flying blind out here!
The instruments
are going crazy.
(WEAKLY) That's comforting.
Wait, what is that?
What on earth?
Oh, no. No. No, no, no!
Brace for impact!
(PUPS YELP)
Whoa!
(ALL GRUNT)
Ugh.
(PUPS GROAN)
(RYDER GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
This doesn't make any sense.
There's no island on the map.
I guess it's time
to update the map.
So what do
we do now?
We've got
to explore the island.
Marshall's
right.
But if we're going
into that jungle,
we need to suit up
for the job.
All right, pups,
these are
your new survival suits.
They've got
everything you need
to stay alive in the jungle.
Protection from the elements.
Safety gear for climbing.
Built-in floatation devices.
(HELMET BEEPS)
Flashlights, compass
and G.P.S.
(COMPASS WHIRS)
Whatever this island
throws at us,
we'll be prepared.
Ready for action,
Ryder, sir!
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(FROGS CROAKING)
This place
is amazing.
Everything
is so huge.
Let's climb
to the top of that cliff
and get a lay of the land.
(FROGS CROAKING)
(VINE CREAKS)
(PUPS GRUNTING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Ugh.
Wow. Look at that view!
Dudes.
It's incredible.
And I've got
the best seat
in the house.
(RUMBLE)
Whoa.
(THUDS)
(YELPS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GASP)
I'm okay!
ALL: Marshall! (GIGGLE)
(ALL GASP)
(WHISPERS)
Marshall!
What? I said I'm okay.
It's kind of my thing.
I crash into something,
then I pop back up
and say, "I'm okay!"
People seem to like it.
Marshall, run!
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
What on earth
is that thing?!
(ROARS)
(PUPS SCREAM)
(GASPS, SCREAMS)
Come on! Go, go, go!
(MARSHALL YELPING)
(PUPS PANTING)
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
Run!
(ROARS)
I am running!
I'm a bulldog, this is as fast
as I can go! (PANTS)
Is that a dinosaur?
I thought those things
were extinct!
(ROARS)
(ALL PANTING)
(SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTS)
(GROWLS)
Don't eat me! Don't eat me!
Marshall!
(DISTANT GROWL)
(SNORTS)
(ROARS)
(YELLING)
(YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
(ROARS)
Get out of here,
you old cranky pants!
(WHINES)
(GROWLS)
(MOANS)
(GROANS)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
You woke her up, didn't you?
Wha-- W-What?
Don't take it personally.
That Spinosaurus is always
cranky after her nap.
Boy, is it good to see
some other pups!
It's just been me
and the dinosaurs
for the last
two and a half years.
(ALL WHIMPERING)
Oh, how rude of me! I'm Rex.
And this is Timmy the T-Rex.
(TIMMY GROANS, RUMBLES)
(STAMMERS)
Timmy is t-t-terrifying.
No, he's not.
You're not terrifying.
You're a good boy,
aren't you, buddy?
Yeah, you're a good boy.
(TIMMY MOANS)
(TIMMY SNORTS)
(GROANS)
H-How are there
dinosaurs here?
How-- How are you here?
What's going on?
I'm sure you got
a lot of questions.
Why don't you let me
show you around,
and I'll do my best
to answer as many as I can.
(CHITTERING)
REX: I've been stranded
on this island
since I fell overboard
during a storm.
The first time
I saw a dinosaur,
I almost jumped out of my fur.
But they're actually
really friendly
when you get to know them.
(TIMMY GRUMBLES)
Come on, follow me.
(REX GRUNTS)
Ha!
MARSHALL: Whoa!
He is so cool.
The pup's got moves,
no doubt about it.
(EXHALES)
(LAUGHS) Whoa--
Wait, whoa, whoa--
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(GRUNTS)
ALL: Marshall!
(GIGGLES)
Sorry about that. (GROANS)
In case you haven't guessed,
I'm the clumsy pup.
It's all good.
Keep trying.
Everybody makes mistakes
when they're learning
something new.
Whoa. Look!
(STEGOSAURUSES RUMBLE)
Oh! Hello.
(BABY CHITTERS)
Ah!
Oh-- Uh...
(BABY GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
They're just shy.
They'll get used
to you soon enough.
Okay, this is me.
Whoa. Rex,
you built all this?
Yep. It's taken me
two years, a hundred
and forty-seven days,
and I'm almost done.
(HORN BLOWS)
(DISTANT THUD)
(BRACHIOSAURUS RUMBLES)
Whoa! Whoa.
All aboard.
Hup.
(GRUNTS)
Oh! Whoa--
Whoa, whoa.
Whoa!
(PUPS LAUGH)
Whoo!
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(RUMBLES)
Thanks for the lift, Nellie!
Hey! (LAUGHS)
(PUPS GIGGLE)
It was always my dream
to build my own treehouse.
When I got stranded out here,
I finally got the chance.
RYDER: Whoa!
This is incredible!
REX: It's all made
out of stuff I found
on the island.
It's amazing how much nature
will give you
if you know where to look.
Welcome to my home sweet home.
It doesn't have
air conditioning,
a big screen TV or Wi-Fi...
(VINE CREAKS)
...but it does the trick.
ZUMA: Wow!
Dude, this is the coolest
treehouse in the world!
It's glamping. I could
totally get behind this.
Plus, being up this high
must give you some privacy
from all the dinosaurs.
(NELLIE RUMBLES)
Ah!
Or maybe not.
(PUPS GIGGLE)
If you really want to see
Dino Island,
there's only one way
to do it.
Do you want to go
for a ride?
(BOTTLE UP BY
BACKSTREET BOYS PLAYS)
(HOWLS)
♪ Something about you
Got me
♪ Like lightning struck
♪ My body
(WHOOPS)
♪ Tell the room
Get out the way
(ALL WHOOPING)
Yeah!
♪ We are made of broken pieces
♪ But that's how
The love gets in
(HOWLS)
Whoo-hoo! (GIGGLES)
♪ You're under my skin
Check it out! Triceratops!
(LOWING)
♪ Ooh, if you're feeling
The love go deeper
♪ And deeper, come down
Whoo-hoo! (GIGGLES)
♪ I don't know
When I'll come back 'round
♪ Keep this forever
♪ And, ooh
I'm studying every feature
Whoa.
♪ I'm speechless
♪ Right now
♪ Take this moment
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
♪ And bottle up this feeling
Hey, little dudes!
♪ When I watch you dancing
♪ I'm under your command
♪ Just one touch you got me
Whoa!
♪ Right in the palm
Of your hand
Whoa!
♪ So take this moment
Whoa.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
(SQUAWKS)
♪ And bottle up this feeling
Hey, girl,
that's some nice flying.
♪ Can't stop time
(CAWS)
♪ But tonight
♪ Is for life
♪ Take this moment
♪ And bottle up this feeling
(REX LAUGHS)
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
(YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
Wow, Rex, that was so cool!
It never gets old.
This island is the greatest
scientific discovery
in the history of the world!
(DINOSAURS LOWING)
(BUZZES)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(INHALES DEEPLY) Ah.
Kitties,
welcome to the first day
of the rest of our lives.
(KITTIES MEWING)
Hey, Humdinger,
stay out of trouble!
Oh, no need to worry,
I've turned over a new leaf.
No more crimes for me.
I'm a changed man.
(SCOFFS) I'll believe that
when I see it.
(CHUCKLES)
This sure beats prison food,
doesn't it, kitties?
(CHUCKLES)
(SLURPING)
(ALL MEOW)
Oh! Garcon! Another round
of milkshakes over here!
(SIGHS)
All right, kitties.
Society has given us
a second chance,
and we're going
to do it right this time.
No more cheating.
(MEOW)
No more lying.
No more
get-rich-quick schemes.
(GROANS)
For the first time in my life,
I'm going to earn
an honest living.
(NEWS REPORT THEME PLAYS)
(SLURPS)
I'm Lilian Ledes,
coming to you live
from a previously
uncharted island
where the PAW Patrol have made
an amazing discovery.
Ugh. The PAW Patrol.
They're still a thing?
They're calling it
Dino Island.
And it's the only place
on Earth where, get this--
dinosaurs still exist.
(ROARS)
(WOMAN GASPS)
Wow! Dinosaurs?
That's incredible!
Who cares about
stinking dinosaurs?
Look behind it, kitties.
Those are diamonds.
Forget earning
an honest living.
(WOMAN GASPS)
If I could get my hands
on those diamonds,
I'd be a kajillionaire!
We're gonna be
back on top, baby.
Whoo-hoo!
(GASPS)
(SCATS) Whoo!
(CACKLES MANIACALLY)
(KITTIES CACKLE)
(NEWS REPORT THEME PLAYS)
Top scientists
from around the world
have arrived on Dino Island.
They'll be working
hand-in-hand
with the PAW Patrol
to study these
incredible creatures
and protect
their fragile ecosystem.
Welcome to Dino Island.
Thanks for coming.
We need all
the scientists
we can get.
Are you kidding?
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
Hi there.
I'm Heidi,
and this is Gene.
Hi.
We're with the Paleontological
Studies Institute.
Well, if you like dinosaurs,
you came to the right place.
The paleontology base camp
is just down that path.
(YELPS)
(STEGOSAURUS RUMBLES)
GENE: That is a real dinosaur.
Oh. This is way scarier
than I imagined.
(LAUGHS)
Great. My lab partner
is a dinosaur expert
who's scared of dinosaurs.
I work in a museum.
I study bones.
I'm not built
for the field. (YELPS)
(HEIDI LAUGHS)
(STEGOSAURUS RUMBLES)
You see? That would
never happen at the museum.
(RUN WILD
BY THUTMOSE & NOMBE PLAYS)
♪ Run wild
♪ I'm on a mission
That I won't stop
♪ No destination
But it's worth a shot
♪ You gotta let me go
♪ Please, outta my way
♪ No rules in the wild
It begins
♪ Naive, so a L is a win
♪ Got a grin on my face
And we're off to the race
♪ Goin' fast
And we never slow down
♪ Head to head
We go pound for pound
♪ Take them out downtown
♪ Flood the town
Cops gonna get down
Whoa!
♪ Run wild
♪ I'm on a mission
And I won't stop
♪ No destination
But it's worth a shot
♪ You gotta let me go
All right, team,
we've got 65 million years
of scientific discovery
to catch up on.
Let's get to work.
♪ You gotta let me go
(GRUNTS)
♪ Ready for war
♪ Got my armor gear
Sharpen your sword
♪ 'Cause the time is near
♪ Gotta do it big
Like Bon Iver
♪ I'm a rock star
On a chandelier
♪ Off the walls, yeah
I'm about to go crazy
♪ Free the beast, ain't nobody
That could tame me
♪ What a thrill
Always seems to amaze me
♪ In the forest with the youth
And they're raving
♪ Dancin' nonstop
'Til the break of dawn
♪ Sheriffs come around
Probably best to run
♪ Fire in my eyes
Can't catch me now
♪ I'm young and numb
Trying to have some fun
♪ Don't judge me
♪ You only live once
Homies in the back
♪ So we gotta live it up
Say "ah."
(ROARS)
(SCREAMS)
♪ Running miles
And running wild
♪ I'm chugging
Like I'm fueling
(SIGHS)
♪ Houston
♪ And tellin' 'em
That I'm comin' up
♪ I'm cruisin'
Huh?
♪ Space boost comin' loose
(CHITTERS)
♪ But all I feel
♪ Is music like
(GASPS)
♪ Nah, nah, nah, nah
(CHITTERING)
♪ Never look back
♪ Nah, nah, nah, nah
♪ Run wild
♪ I'm on a mission
And I won't stop
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
♪ No destination
But it's worth a shot
♪ You gotta let me go
♪ You gotta let me go ♪
Uh, Rex, we're out of water.
Ugh, the water wheel's
jammed again.
Sometimes stuff
from the river
gets stuck in it.
(CREAKING, SLOSHING)
(GRUNTING)
There we go.
Ouch!
(CREATURE TRILLS)
(CHITTERS)
Did you just
throw this stick at me?
Hey, come back here!
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CREATURE SNORTS)
(YELPS)
(SCREECHES)
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS, CHUCKLES)
That's not much
of a roar for a T-Rex.
(TRILLS)
(CHITTERS)
Oh,
I see what's going on here.
You want to play fetch.
(SQUAWKS)
Why didn't you say so?
You're talking to
the original fetch master.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTS)
(MURMURS)
Okay. One more throw.
But then I got to get
back to work. Deal?
(SQUEAKS)
(GRUNTS)
(CHITTERS)
No!
(WHIMPERS, YELPS)
(SCREAMS)
Hang on, I'm coming!
(WHIMPERS, SQUEALS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(FRIGHTENED SQUEALING)
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
(SQUAWKING)
(YELPS)
I'm right behind you!
(WHINES)
It's gonna be okay!
Grab on!
(WHIMPERING)
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
Oh, no.
Please be a little one,
please be a little one.
(T-REX SQUEAKS)
It's not a little one!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(GASPS) I got you!
(GRUNTS)
(MARSHALL PANTING)
You okay?
(TRILLS EAGERLY)
(CHUCKLES) I think that's
enough fetch for one day.
(ENGINE CLANKING)
(FOGHORN BLARES)
Dino Island has the biggest
diamond deposit in the world.
And the two of you
are going
to help me get it.
Phase one of the plan
is led by Harper Cutlass,
our expert survival guide.
You're here to help us
get through the jungle
and make sure
we don't get eaten by any
of those nasty dinosaurs.
Don't worry.
I'm a master of stealth.
Those dinosaurs
will never hear us coming.
(YELPS)
(KITTIES YOWL)
Everything's fine!
Nothing to worry about.
Okay.
Phase two of our plan
is where you come into play.
Alistair Stonewall.
Mining and explosives expert.
There's nothing
I can't dig.
Nothing I can't drill.
And if all else fails,
there's nothing
I can't blast
to smithereens! (LAUGHS)
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
Uh, love the enthusiasm.
But let's save it
for the diamonds, shall we?
Land ho!
Whoo-hoo!
Ah... There it is.
Dino Island. (CACKLES)
(RUMBLES)
Hey! (CHUCKLES)
(PUPS GIGGLE)
That's all of them.
The dinos are squeaky clean.
Marshall! There you are.
We were wondering
where you went.
Uh, you're not gonna
believe this,
but I think
I made a new friend.
(CHITTERS)
(CHUCKLES) He's a little shy.
(GASPS) He's so cute!
I saved him
when he fell
in the river,
and he's been
following me
ever since.
(GASPS) No fair!
I want a dinosaur B.F.F.
(GRUNTS)
(SQUEALS)
It's me and you, buddy.
Best friends forever.
(SCREECHING)
Oh-- Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
Okay, stop, stop, stop!
Never mind!
(HISSES)
(PUPS AND RYDER LAUGH)
So, does
this little guy
have a name?
Not that I know of.
Well, we should
give him one.
It's not every day
you get to name
a dinosaur.
Let's see.
You're bright red
with a white tummy
and a little bit of green
on your tail.
We should call you...
Rhubarb!
Rhubarb?!
I think he likes
his name.
Too late
to change it now.
Well, if he's happy,
I'm happy.
Rhubarb it is!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREECHES)
What was that?
(CHUCKLES)
Rhubarb's still
working on his roar.
(SNICKERS)
(ENGINES PUTTER)
(CREAKS, SQUEALS)
(GASPS) Well, I'll be.
(BRACHIOSAURUS LOWS)
(WHOOPS, LAUGHS)
Look at the size
of that thing.
Ugh, well,
we don't have all day.
Get that thing
out of the way.
Stand back. I got this.
(KNUCKLES CRACK)
(LOWS MOCKINGLY)
(BABBLES)
(TRILLS, CHITTERS)
What are you doing?
That is my dinosaur call.
I'm trying to get
his attention.
Aw, isn't that cute?
Not gonna work, though.
Out of my way!
(YELPS)
Coming through! (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, LOWS)
What do you think
you're doing?
I'm not letting
this Cretaceous cretin
stand in my way.
(MEWS)
(HORN HONKS)
(YELPS)
(MEOWS)
Move it!
Get out of my way,
I've got places to be!
Scoot! Shoo! Vamoose!
(ROARS)
(BRACHIOSAURUS GROANS)
Whoa.
What?! That wasn't my fault.
He tripped on his own.
You saw it, right, kitties?
(KITTIES MEW)
(WAILS DEEPLY)
Okay, Rhubarb,
we've got to work
on that roar of yours.
You're a T-Rex.
You should have a big, loud,
commanding roar!
(GRUNTS)
Here, do what I do.
Put your feet apart like this.
Now stand up straight.
(MURMURS)
Chest forward.
(GRUNTS)
But keep your tail
in the air.
Take a deep breath.
(INHALES)
Now... roar! (ROARS)
(ALL ROAR)
(SCREECHES WEAKLY)
Okay, not bad.
It was a good start.
You'll get there.
You just need
to stick with it.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(BEEPS)
Hey, Heidi.
How's it going
out there?
Ryder!
There's a Brachiosaurus
in trouble!
(LOWS)
(REX GASPS)
Where are you?
We're on the far side
of the island.
I'm sending you
the coordinates now.
We're on our way.
Come on, pups!
No dino's too big,
no pup's too small.
(ENGINES WHIRRING)
RYDER: Pups,
get ready to launch.
(MACHINERY BEEPS)
(CHIMES)
(HOWLS)
(SCREEN CHIMES)
(SIREN WHOOPS)
(BEEPS)
Ready for launch!
(ENGINE POWERS UP)
RYDER: Marshall, go!
(PING)
(WHOOSHES)
(ENGINE ROARS)
(HOWLS)
(WHIRS, BEEPS)
RYDER: Skye, go!
(BEEPS, WHOOSHES)
(ENGINE ROARS)
(ENGINE REVS, BLASTS)
RYDER: Zuma, go!
(ENGINE ROARS)
RYDER: Rocky, go!
(PULSES, WHOOSHES)
RYDER: Rubble, go!
(BEEPS)
(RUBBLE HOWLS)
RYDER: Chase, go!
(BEEPS, WHOOSHES)
(CHASE HOWLS)
(SIREN WAILING)
(PUPS HOWL)
(MARSHALL HOWLS)
(SIREN WAILS)
GENE: Oh, thank goodness
you're here.
What happened?
I don't know.
He must have slipped.
(LOWS SOFTLY)
(WAILS)
We don't have much time!
Chase, Rocky,
let's get him strapped in.
You got it, Ryder!
Dropping in. (GRUNTS)
Let's do this.
(HOWLS)
Marshall, I need you
to use your winch
to pull that
Brachiosaurus
out of there.
I'm on it!
Stabilizers down.
Here we go.
(LOWS)
Let's flip and clip.
Deploying net.
MARSHALL:
Here comes the hook!
The Brachiosaurus
is secure.
All right, Marshall,
haul him up.
Copy that.
Okay, Marshall,
no mistakes.
(WINCH WHIRS)
Dino's on the move!
Bringing him up
slow and steady.
(LOWS)
(GROANS)
(BEEPING)
Something's stuck
in the winch!
(CREAKING)
Hang on! I'll fix it. (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(HYDRAULICS HISSING)
No, no. No, no, no, no!
No, no!
Marshall!
(YELPING)
(GROANS, GRUNTS)
(PANTS, GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
Look out!
Whoa!
My truck!
(LOWS, RUMBLES)
Oh, no.
How are we gonna get
that dino out now?
What can we do to help?
(TRICERATOPS LOWING)
Everybody, grab a rope!
(TRICERATOPS RUMBLES)
(ENGINE REVS)
RYDER: Three, two, one,
pull!
(ENGINES REVVING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
RYDER: It's stuck!
RYDER: Come on!
(ENGINE STRAINS)
(GASPS)
It's working!
(BOTH HOWL)
(RUMBLES, LOWS)
(PUPS CHEER, LAUGH)
Great work, team.
Nicely done,
pups!
(ROARS)
(LOWS)
CHASE: You gotta watch
your step next time, big guy.
He seems so steady
on his feet.
I wonder what made him fall.
(MEOWS)
(HEAVY SNORES)
We're here!
(TIRES SCREECH)
Oh!
(HORN HONKS)
Uh-huh?
Stay behind me.
Who knows
what kind of monsters
are hiding in these shadows.
(TWIG SNAPS)
(GASPS)
(CHIRPS)
(SCREAMS)
(CHITTERS)
(CHUCKLES)
Sorry, I-- I thought
it would be bigger.
(SQUEALS, CHITTERS)
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna tell anybody
you scream like that.
Ooh. Check it out.
This is igneous rock.
The whole island is sitting
on top of a giant volcano!
A volcano.
Not sure I like
the sound of that.
It's nothing
to worry about.
This baby's been dormant
for thousands of years.
It's not waking up
for anybody.
(GASPS) It's even sparklier
than it was on TV!
I'm gonna be rich.
(KITTIES MEW)
No, filthy rich.
No! Filthy, stinking rich!
(CACKLES)
Mm!
(CRUNCHES)
Ow!
(SNARLS)
Get off me! Get off me!
(SQUEAKS, CHITTERS)
Ow!
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
Don't worry,
I'll set some traps.
Teach these bitey little
critters some manners.
(CREAKS, SNAPS)
(YELPS)
Everything's fine.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
Well, what are we
standing around for?
Let's mine these diamonds
and get out of here
before the PAW Patrol
starts sniffing around.
(CHITTERING)
(YELLS)
(BANG, TWANG)
Ooh. (CHUCKLES)
That's not good.
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
(CHITTERING LAUGHTER)
(GRUNTS)
We're going to need
a little more power.
(PICK CLANGS)
(ENGINE REVS, SPUTTERS)
(SQUEAL)
Hey, Humdinger!
You sure you
can handle that thing?
(REVVING, SPUTTERING)
What? I can't hear you!
(BABBLES)
(BABBLES, SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(DINOSAURS CACKLE)
Ha, ha, ha.
You little lizards
think this is funny?
I'll give you something
to laugh about.
Assemble the drill!
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
Let's get this party started!
(LAUGHS)
(GIGGLES)
(BRACHIOSAURUS LOWS)
(SQUEAKING CROW)
(METALLIC THUD)
(YELPS)
You really smashed
that sucker up good,
didn't you?
Yep.
Eh! Don't worry about it.
Mistakes happen.
Rescue pups aren't
supposed to make mistakes.
(METALLIC THUD,
CLATTERING)
That's not true.
Everybody makes mistakes.
Not you.
Are you kidding?
I make more mistakes
than anyone.
You do?
You look up
and see a finished treehouse.
But what you don't see
is all the mistakes
it took to get there.
Making mistakes is how
you learn and get better.
Well, that...
and never giving up.
(STRAINS)
All right, let her rip!
(ENGINE REVS)
(CACKLES)
Hang on, kitties.
(BOTH CHIRP)
(BLADES WHIR)
(HUMDINGER CACKLES)
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Wow--
(YELPS)
(CRASHING)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS)
(CLANGS, CLATTERING)
What kind of cut-rate
mining equipment
is this?!
Hey, it's not my fault.
The diamond is too hard.
I've never seen
anything like it.
So, what do we do?
When in doubt...
we blast it out!
(GIGGLES)
(SING-SONGY) Blast it out,
blast it out, blast it out!
I said we blast it out,
Whoo-hoo!
(CHITTERS)
(FEARFUL SQUEAL)
Everybody stand back.
Oh, oh, oh! Can I press
the dynamite plunger thingy?
Can I? Please?
(SIGHS) Fine.
Just stop making that face.
You're freaking me out!
(GIGGLES)
I've wanted to do this
ever since I started
watching cartoons.
(HUMS SHAVE AND A HAIRCUT)
(CLICKS)
(DISTANT RUMBLE)
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
(ALL LOWING)
(LOWS)
(GRUNTING)
(SQUEALS)
(DINOSAURS SQUEAL, BELLOW)
(WHOOPS)
I love it
when it goes boom!
(MEOWS)
Ooh.
(CHUCKLES) Wow!
(CACKLES) It worked!
It worked! (LAUGHS)
We're gonna need
more dynamite.
A lot more dynamite.
(TOOL CLANGS)
Huh?
(METALLIC RATTLING)
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
What is that?
Do you guys hear
that sound?
It's my stomach.
Those baby dinosaurs
ate all my pup treats.
(LOW RUMBLE)
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
Somebody get
this guy a snack!
(ALL SCREAM)
(DINOSAURS ROAR)
Whoa!
(GASPS)
It's a stampede! (YELPS)
(DINOSAURS ROAR)
BOTH: Whoa!
(MARSHALL WHIMPERS)
(ROCKY YELPING)
(BRACHIOSAURUS LOWS)
They're heading
straight for
the geology camp!
Come on, pups,
let's roll!
(PUPS HOWL)
I can't go on the rescue.
I've got no truck!
(ENGINE REVS)
(ENGINE WHIRS)
(WHOOSHES)
(PUPS HOWL)
(MACHINERY HISSES)
Anybody need a ride?
Come on, Rhubarb,
let's go!
SCIENTIST: Our hypothesis
is that lava tubes running
underneath the dormant volcano
kept the island warm enough
for these dinosaurs
to survive the Ice Age.
CAMERAMAN: And cut!
We got it.
(CRUNCHES)
(SCREAMS)
Take cover!
SCIENTIST: Whoa!
(GASPS)
Oh, look out!
(YELPS)
MAN: Help, help!
WOMAN: It's a stampede!
MAN: Whoa!
(GASPS, YELLS)
(STEGOSAURUS GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS, YELPS)
(YELPS, GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(ENGINE WHOOSHES)
Ryder! Someone's caught
in the stampede!
Copy that.
We're on our way.
(PANTING) There she is!
HEIDI: Help, over here!
Hang on!
I'm going in.
(ENGINE ROARS)
There's too many dinos.
We can't get in there!
Well, who's gonna save her?
Come on, Rhubarb,
it's up to us!
Hi-yah!
(DINOSAURS GRUNTING)
Yeah! Marshall!
I can see her!
She's just up ahead!
Marshall,
I'm dropping a rescue line.
(BEEPS)
(WHIRRING)
Come on, Rhubarb,
we've got to get in close!
(YELPS)
I can't hang on!
Steady, steady.
Help!
Now! (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS, YELPS)
It's gonna be okay!
(PANTS) I can't
hang on anymore!
I just need you to hang on
for five more seconds.
You can let go in five...
(PANTS)
...four...
three...
(YELLS)
...two...
(GRUNTS)
...one!
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAM FADES)
(SCREAM GETS LOUDER)
Yeah!
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS, WHOOPS)
Did you see that?!
SKYE: Got her.
Nice moves, Marshall.
Now get out of there.
(WHISTLES)
(RHUBARB CHITTERS)
(TRILLS)
You ready, buddy?
(SQUEAKS)
Let's do this.
(GRUNTS) Oof!
(MARSHALL GRUNTING)
Oof.
(RHUBARB WHIMPERS)
No! Rhubarb!
(BRACHIOSAURUS LOWS)
RYDER: (MUFFLED) Marshall?
Marshall?
You took a pretty hard fall
out there.
The good thing
is nothing's broken.
Where's Rhubarb?
We don't know.
He got lost
in the stampede.
I have to find him.
You need to rest.
The team's out
looking for him now.
Rhubarb could be hurt.
This is all my fault.
No, it's not.
It was an accident.
Accidents seem to happen
a lot around me.
I used to be funny
being the clumsy pup.
I'd fall down
and say "I'm okay"
and everything would be fine.
But now it's not fine.
I keep making mistakes.
I almost got eaten
by a dinosaur.
I wrecked my truck.
And this time,
when I messed up,
I hurt my friend.
Sometimes I think
you'd all be better off
without a clumsy pup like me.
Don't say that.
You're only focusing
on your mistakes.
Think of all
the good things
you've done.
Do you remember
the first time we met?
(PUPPIES YIP FAINTLY)
(BARKS, PANTS)
Welcome to
the PAW Patrol tryouts.
Good luck out there, pups.
Let's see what you can do.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(PUPPIES BARK)
(GRUNTS)
(PUPPY BARKS)
(GRUNTING)
Whoa! (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTS)
(PUPPIES BARK)
(MARSHALL GRUNTS, PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS) Whoa!
(PUPPY BARKS)
Hup.
Yeah-- Uh-- Uh!
(GRUNTS)
(PUPPY BARKS, PANTS)
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
Oof.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Ryder,
come see this.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
(GRUNTS) Whoa.
Whoa! (GRUNTS)
(THUNDER CLAPS)
I can do this.
(GRUNTING)
RYDER: I didn't
pick you because
you never made mistakes.
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
(YELPS, YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
RYDER: I picked you
because you're the pup
that never gives up.
(MARSHALL GROANS)
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
I don't need you
to be perfect.
I just need you to give it
everything you've got.
Can you do that
for me?
You can count
on me, Ryder.
(ENGINE WHIRS)
(ENGINE WHINES)
Is he okay?
Did you find Rhubarb?
No, not yet.
It's too dark
out there.
We can't see a thing.
But we're not giving up.
We'll start the search again
first thing in the morning.
Hey!
Where are you going?
I'm going
to find Rhubarb.
It's pitch black
out there.
There's no way you're gonna
find him in the dark.
I have to try. I can't just
sit around till morning.
The jungle's no joke
at night.
It's easy to get lost
out there.
I'm not giving up on him.
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
Rhubarb!
(DINOSAUR LOWS DISTANTLY)
Rhubarb?
(CREATURE SNARLS DISTANTLY)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(TWIG SNAPS)
Hello? Rhubarb?
(FAINT GROWL)
(WHIMPERS)
(YELPS)
(PANTING)
(ECHOING) Rhubarb?!
Rhubarb!
Where are you? (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
Rhubarb!
(GRUNTS, YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHS)
(GROANS)
I'm okay.
Yeah, I'm okay.
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(SPRING CLICKS)
(GRUNTS, YELPS)
Whoa!
What's going on? (GRUNTS)
Get me out of here! (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS) Help!
(CHITTERING)
(GRUNTS) Hmm.
HUMDINGER: Put them closer!
Pack it in there!
It's gonna be
the Fourth of July!
I think we've got
enough dynamite, boss.
It's enough
when I say it's enough!
Keep going! (CACKLES)
HARPER: Hey!
Guess what.
I caught
my first dinosaur.
Humdinger!
(SCOFFS)
That's not a dinosaur.
It's one of those dogs
from the PAW Patrol.
There are
so many of them,
I can never remember
their names.
Oh, oh, oh!
That one's Marshall!
He's my nephew's favorite!
(GASPS, SPUTTERS)
If I had known
you had a nephew
that liked the PAW Patrol,
I never would have hired you!
What are you
doing here?
Well,
we started out drilling,
but now we've moved on
to blasting.
Are you out of your mind?!
That's a dormant volcano!
If you set that thing off,
you're going to destroy
the island.
Well, I guess that's just
the cost of doing business.
Keep an eye on this one.
Those pups are slippery.
Don't let him
out of your sight.
Don't worry.
He's not going
anywhere.
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, SIGHS)
(PANTING)
You won't get away
with this.
(MOCKING) "You won't
get away with this."
(CHUCKLES)
I'm afraid it's you
who won't be
getting away.
(GROWLS)
ALISTAIR: That's all of it.
We're officially
out of dynamite.
Nice work, Marshall.
You didn't find Rhubarb,
you got yourself caught,
and now Humdinger's gonna
blow up the island
while you're stuck here
doing nothing.
So much for being the pup
who never gives up.
Who said anything
about giving up?
Rex?
What are you doing here?
I followed your trail.
And it's a good thing
I did.
Now let's get you
out of here.
What about her?
Heh.
I'll handle it.
(TRILLS, CLICKS)
(ALL CHITTERING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
What is this?
A bone-shaped cookie?
(RUSTLING)
(DINOSAURS CHITTERING)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS) They love
those pup treats.
Humdinger's got
the whole volcano wired
with dynamite!
HUMDINGER: You might want
to plug your ears!
Wait, no, stop!
(GRUNTS)
(WHOOSHING, RUMBLING)
(BOTH YELP, GRUNT)
(GASPS)
(PANTS)
(DIAMONDS CLINKING)
Whoo-hoo!
(CACKLES)
(CACKLES SHRILLY)
Whoa!
(CACKLES, YELPS)
(SNICKERS)
(GRUNTS, YELPS)
(WHOOPS)
Now that's what I call
having a blast!
(CACKLES)
(LOW RUMBLING)
(BOTH GASP)
The volcano!
We have to warn Ryder.
Come on!
REX: Ryder!
MARSHALL: Ryder!
Ryder!
Marshall! Rex!
Where were you?
Humdinger's here!
Humdinger?!
He just set off
a thousand sticks of dynamite
on the side of the volcano.
(DISTANT BOOM)
(PUPS WINCE)
(RUMBLES, WHOOSHES)
(PANTING)
Whoa!
What on earth?
Oh, no.
(LAVA BOMBS WHISTLING,
BOOMING)
Rhubarb's still out there!
(WHOOSHING)
RYDER: Look out!
(PUPS YELP)
We've got to get
all the people
and the dinosaurs to safety.
We're on it!
What about Rhubarb?
Don't worry. I'll find him.
Then you're
gonna need this.
My truck!
Meet us
at the caverns.
(ENGINE REVS)
I'm fired up!
(ENGINE RUMBLES)
(WHISTLES)
Where's Timmy?
When I was fixing
Marshall's truck,
I made a few upgrades
to your ride, too.
(THUDS)
(ROARS)
Whoa!
Let's roll out!
We've got an island to save.
(ENGINE FADES DISTANTLY)
(SCIENTISTS SCREAMING)
This job is
much more dangerous
than I thought it would be.
BOTH: Whoa!
We've got to get
everyone to the caverns.
It's the only place
we'll be safe.
Come on!
Let's move it, people!
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
(SCIENTISTS MURMURING)
Everybody on!
(SCIENTISTS SHOUTING)
(WHOOSHES, BOOMS)
(ENGINE REVS)
Okay, go, go!
SCIENTIST: Wait up!
Wait up!
(ALISTAIR GRUNTS, SIGHS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
HUMDINGER: Over here!
Help me get the big one.
(CHUCKLES)
The bigger they are,
the more they're worth!
The truck's full
of diamonds.
We're already rich.
Let's get out
of here, man!
But look at the size
of this thing!
You think there's
a lesson here about
not being too greedy?
No, I don't.
Now get over here
and lift!
(ALL STRAINING)
Come on, you weaklings,
lift with your backs.
(ALL STRAIN)
(FRANTIC YOWLS)
(HONKING)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS, STRAINS)
Lift!
Uh, we should really
get out of here.
No! I am not leaving
this diamond.
(STRAINS)
Huh?
Oh! (FRANTIC YELPING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(LAVA BUBBLING)
No!
(KITTIES SOB)
(SQUAWKS)
GENE: Hey, hey, hey!
(SMACKING)
(CHITTERS)
Come on,
little buddy.
Come on.
(SQUEALS)
We got to get you
out of here.
(BOOM)
Come on now. Come on.
(DINOSAUR CHITTERS)
(GASPS)
Get down from that tree.
No, no, no, no, no!
Get up in the tree!
(SCIENTISTS PANTING)
(SQUEALS FEARFULLY)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(SCIENTISTS
AND DINOSAUR SCREAM)
(SCIENTISTS SCREAM)
(CHITTERING, SQUEALING)
All right, Timmy,
I'm gonna grab them.
Come on, little guys.
Hop on.
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
(MACHINERY WHIRS)
(HOWLS)
(DINOSAURS SQUEALING)
I'm happy to give you a ride,
but you have to promise
not to steal
any more of my pup treats.
(CHITTERS)
Oh, come on!
(DINOSAURS GIGGLE)
(DEVICE RINGS, BEEPS)
This is Gene and Heidi.
We're stuck in a mudslide.
We need an evac... ASAP!
Copy that, Gene.
I've got eyes
on your location.
(WHOOSH)
(DISTANT BOOM)
(GASPS)
(JET RATTLING)
(ALERTS BEEPING)
Okay, change of plan.
I can't fly.
There's too much ash
in the air.
We're gonna have to do
this rescue from the ground.
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
Chase, I'm gonna need backup.
CHASE: Already on my way.
(WHOOSHES)
(ENGINE ROARS)
(BEEPS)
Marshall, this is Ryder.
Any sign of Rhubarb?
MARSHALL: Not yet.
But I'm not coming in
until I find him.
(LAVA BOMB WHISTLES)
(ENGINE ROARS)
There they are!
HEIDI: Over here!
GENE: Help!
SKYE: Hang on!
We're coming!
Skye, I'm gonna fire
my grappling hook
across to you.
(BEEPS)
SKYE: Ready when you are.
Fire!
(CHIMES)
Nice shot.
CHASE: Bullseye!
CHASE: Get on!
(GENE GRUNTS)
(GROANS) Got it!
Whoa.
(GASPING)
And up we go!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(SQUEALS, CHITTERS)
(GASPS)
(SCIENTISTS YELLING)
SKYE: Climb toward me!
(BOTH GRUNT)
Climb, climb,
climb!
Uh-oh. Hill!
(BOTH GRUNT)
Oh-- Whoa!
(HEIDI YELPS)
(BOTH GROANING)
Okay, let's try that again.
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
If this rope hits that rock,
it's going to cut it in half!
Okay, I'm climbing,
I'm climbing!
(PANTING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
You're
almost there!
Grab on!
Oh, No, no, no, no, no!
(SCREAMS)
BOTH: Whoa!
This is getting ridiculous!
It's now or never.
Time to take the high road.
(GRUNTS)
(ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
SKYE: Got them!
(LAUGHS)
(DINOSAUR WHOOPS)
CHASE: Yeah!
Nice catch, Skye!
Hang on.
(ENGINE ROARS)
Rhubarb! Rhubarb!
Rhubarb!
Rhubarb?
Rhubarb, where are you?
Come on, buddy,
we've got to get out of here!
(LEAVES RUSTLE)
(RUSTLING CONTINUES)
Rhubarb!
Well, look who it is.
(YELPS) Humdinger!
(HUMDINGER CACKLES)
Look what
you've done!
Oh, no.
You're not going
to pin this on me.
You and the PAW Patrol
love to blame
old Humdinger
for everything!
Where are the rest
of your friends now,
little puppy dog?
(GRUNTS)
It's just you and me.
(WHIMPERS)
(ROARS)
(SCREAMS)
Yeah, Rhubarb!
(GASPS)
(ROARS)
(SQUEALS)
(SCREAMING SHRILLY)
Now that's a roar!
(LOWS)
(PAW PATROL PANTING)
Everybody, get under cover!
We'll be safe in the cavern.
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(DINOSAURS LOWING)
SCIENTIST:
Come on, come on!
Is that the last of the dinos?
Is everybody safe?
No. Marshall and Rhubarb
are still out there.
Don't worry.
We'll be out of this soon.
We're gonna take cover
in the cavern.
Let's clear a path!
♪ We're going places
We've never been
♪ Off to the races
We about to win
♪ I feel amazing
Ten out of ten
♪ Let's go
(BEEPING)
Ooh...
♪ Hands up if you're ready
♪ Hold up, keep it steady
Rhubarb, what are you doing?
♪ Go off like confetti
♪ Hold on tight
♪ You better work
Ooh-ooh
♪ Let's get to work
Yeah, Rhubarb!
Nice moves! You're a natural!
(WHIRRING)
♪ Work, work, work, work ♪
(GROANS)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
RYDER: Marshall!
Marshall!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS)
We're trapped!
Everybody, stand back!
(LAVA BUBBLES, HISSES)
It's not working!
There's not enough water!
If I can get up that cliff
and release that water,
we might stand a chance.
Marshall,
what are you doing?
On my signal,
point the water cannons
straight down.
(BABBLES)
Ready...
aim...
fire!
(ENGINE WHIRS)
He's trying to cross it.
It's working!
(SIZZLING, BUBBLING)
Marshall, hurry!
Huh?
(SIZZLING, BUBBLING)
(GASPS, SQUEAKS)
(RUMBLES)
(GRUNTS)
No, no!
Come on, come on!
No, no! (YELPS)
(CROWD GASPS)
(MARSHALL YELPS)
Marshall!
Rhubarb, get out of there!
We're gonna have to jump.
Three, two,
one, now!
(GROWLS)
(MARSHALL GRUNTING)
(YELPS, YELLS)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(PUPS HOWL)
He did it!
This is not a good week
to be Marshall's firetruck.
(RHUBARB CHITTERS)
(MARSHALL GRUNTS)
I got it from here,
buddy.
You stay safe.
(WHINES)
(GRUNTS)
What is he
doing?
He's trying to put out
the biggest fire of his life.
He better be quick.
We don't have much time.
(WHOOSHES, BOOMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS, GRUNTS)
(WHOOSHES, BOOMS)
(GRUNTS)
(DEBRIS CLATTERING)
(GASPS, YELPS)
Rhubarb, look out!
(SQUAWKS)
That was close.
Oh, no.
(GRUNTS) No, no. No!
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTS)
Marshall!
(YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELPS, GRUNTS)
(RUBBLE AND RYDER GASP)
(WHINES)
Come on, Marshall, get up.
Get up.
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(GRUNTS, YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(GRUNTS, YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
RYDER: I didn't pick you
because you never
made mistakes.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
I can do this.
RYDER: I picked you because...
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
...you're the pup
that never gives up.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
(GROANS)
I can do this.
(CHEERING)
He's okay.
It's not over yet.
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINS)
(PANTS)
(WHOOSHES)
(DISTANT YELLING)
(SCATTERED SHOUTING)
(STRAINS)
Come on!
(GRUNTING)
(PANTS)
(STRAINS)
MAN: Oh, no.
(GASPS)
MAN: Don't look!
(STRAINS)
(OVERLAPPING MURMURS)
Come on!
(YELLS)
(RUMBLING)
(WHOOSHES)
(RUMBLING, SIZZLING)
(LAVA CRACKLES)
(STEAM HISSES)
(GRUNTING)
Ryder?
Pups?
Is everyone okay?
(GASPS) Ryder!
Marshall!
(MARSHALL PANTS)
(LAUGHTER)
(PUPS CHEER AND HOWL)
That's why
I picked you.
Because you're the pup
that never gives up.
You did it, Marshall.
You saved us.
You saved all of us.
(DINOSAURS LOWING, CHITTERING)
(CHITTERING)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SQUAWKS)
(DINOSAURS CHITTER)
(BABY STEGOSAURUS SQUEALS)
(YELPS)
(SPINOSAURUS GRUMBLES)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
I'm just happy
everyone's okay.
(SQUAWKS, GRUNTS)
Rhubarb! Whoa... whoa.
Oof-- (GRUNTS)
(SNUFFLES)
Wha--
Oh!
(GROUP CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
I'm happy
to see you,
too, buddy.
(ALL LAUGH)
Nice work, Marshall.
We'll have this jungle
growing back in no time.
So whatever happened
to that Humdinger guy?
I gave him a choice.
He could go back to jail
or he could work it off.
(GRUNTS)
He's gonna be
on fertilizer duty
for a long time.
(GROANS) How much of this
prehistoric poop is there?!
(ALL YELP)
They eat
a thousand pounds
of plants a day.
You do the math!
(CACKLING)
(DINOSAURS CACKLE)
(GRUMBLES)
Wha-- Oh!
Ugh. (GRUMBLES)
I will never
forgive you
for this.
(SCATTERED CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
Hey, everyone,
gather round.
♪ Oh, you just gotta fly
♪ Reach up and touch the sky
♪ Find there's a new horizon
(CROWD CHEERS)
♪ Out there waiting for you
All right, Marshall,
take it away.
Rex, you've been
taking care
of this island
and these dinosaurs
since the day you got here.
You've shown us all that
once you set your mind
to something
there's nothing
you can't do.
(APPLAUSE)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(LAUGHS) Yeah!
(WHIMPERS)
Aw, thanks, guys.
You're brave, you're kind,
and you never give up.
So it's time
to make it official.
Rex, I'm proud to present you
with your
very own pup tag,
making you
a permanent member
of the PAW Patrol
and the caretaker
of Dino Island.
Way to go, Rex!
Way to go!
(LAUGHS)
Yeah!
Way to go, Rex.
(CROWD AND PUPS CHEER)
(LAUGHS)
(CROWD APPLAUDS, WHOOPING)
Our world is filled
with mysteries and wonder.
And it's our job
to protect it.
These dinosaurs have survived
on this island
for millions of years.
And we promise
to do everything we can
to keep them safe forever.
(CROWD CHEERS)
(WHOOPING)
Yeah!
♪ There is a new horizon
(PUPS HOWL)
♪ Out there waiting for you
(ROARS)
(DINOSAURS LOWING)
♪ There is a new horizon
(SQUAWKING)
♪ Out there waiting for you ♪
(PUPS ROAR)
(CHITTERS)
(GASPS)
(ROARS)
(BOTTLE UP BY
BACKSTREET BOYS PLAYS)
♪ Something about you got me
♪ Like lightning
Struck my body
♪ Tell the room
Get out the way
♪ We are made
Of broken pieces
♪ But that's how
The love gets in
♪ You're under my skin
♪ And even if I can stop it
(HOWLS)
♪ I would change
Exactly nothing
♪ Not a word that I could say
♪ To sum up how you make me
Feel like I got everything
♪ It's something
That you bring
♪ And I can't stop time
♪ But tonight
♪ It's for life
♪ Take this moment
♪ And bottle up this feeling
♪ 'Cause when
I watch you dancing
♪ I'm under your command
♪ Just one touch and you
Got me right in the palm
♪ Of your hand
(ROARS)
♪ So take this moment
(CHITTERING)
♪ And bottle up this feeling
♪ Ooh, if you're
Feeling the love
♪ Go deeper and deeper
♪ Come down
♪ I don't know when
I'll come back 'round
♪ Keep this forever and ooh
♪ I'm studying every feature
♪ I'm speechless right now
♪ And just one look
Could take me out
♪ And I can't stop time
♪ But tonight
♪ It's for life
♪ Take this moment
♪ And bottle up this feeling
♪ 'Cause when
I watch you dancing
♪ I'm under your command
♪ Just one touch you got me
♪ Right in the palm
♪ Of your hand
♪ So take this moment
♪ And bottle up this feeling
♪ Underneath these lights
♪ I want to never leave
♪ Can I keep you close to me
♪ Right where I want to be
♪ This just feels so right
♪ Tell me
Is this make-believe?
♪ How did this come to be
♪ It's our reality tonight
♪ So take this moment
♪ And bottle up this feeling
♪ Take this moment
♪ And bottle up
This feeling
♪ Oh
♪ 'Cause when
I watch you dancing
♪ I'm under
Your command
♪ Just one touch you got me
♪ Right in the palm
♪ Of your hand
♪ So take this moment
♪ Take this moment
♪ And bottle up this feeling
♪ Can I hear you say
♪ Hear you say
♪ Ooh-ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪